{
    "id": "0b680ad6b1524aef89dc1058c68b4cb1",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We are …………………………….. for your long, newsy letter.",
            "description": "Grateful means thankful.",
            "answers": [
                "greatful",
                "grateful"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Collecting stamps gives him tremendous ………………………………..",
            "description": "Gratification means satisfaction.",
            "answers": [
                "gratuity",
                "gratification",
                "gratitude"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How can I express my …………………………….. for your help?",
            "description": "Gratitude means gratefulness.",
            "answers": [
                "gratification",
                "grateness",
                "gratitude"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The wheat was ………………………………. into flour.",
            "description": "Ground is the past tense of grind.",
            "answers": [
                "grounded",
                "grinded",
                "ground"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Singing in the shower is …………………………….. with him.",
            "description": "Habitual means regular or normal.",
            "answers": [
                "habit",
                "habitual",
                "habituated"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ………………………………. the clothes yet?",
            "description": "The past tense of hang is hung when we are talking about hanging things.",
            "answers": [
                "hanged",
                "hang",
                "hung"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ………………………………… the way to great a friend.",
            "description": "Hardly can mean by no means.",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly",
                "scarcely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… the doctor’s advice or you will be sorry.",
            "description": "To heed is to follow.",
            "answers": [
                "Heed",
                "Haed",
                "Heed to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The millionaire’s only ……………………………. was his son.",
            "description": "Heir means inheritor.",
            "answers": [
                "hair",
                "heir",
                "hare"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The family has a large ……………………………….. fortune.",
            "description": "Hereditary means inherited.",
            "answers": [
                "hereditary",
                "constitutional",
                "congenital"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………………………. of food was found in the cave.",
            "description": "A hoard is a stockpile.",
            "answers": [
                "hoard",
                "horde",
                "hord"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A …………………………… of Tartars invaded Europe.",
            "description": "A horde is a mob or multitude.",
            "answers": [
                "hoard",
                "hord",
                "horde"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}